Once his, always his.
Only Mine is a thriller, drama, tv movie film directed by Michael Civille.
Tormented and left for dead by a scorned lover, a woman finds the strength
within herself to recover and retaliate against her abuser.
Julie Dillon, played by Amber Midthunder.
David Barragan, played by Brett Zimmerman.
Chief Dodd, played by Chris Browning.
Karen Dillon, played by Claudia Ferri.
Sergeant Miller, played by Walter Fauntleroy.
Tommy, played by Lorenzo James Henrie.
Mine is a 2016 psychological thriller war film written and directed by Fabio
Guaglione and Fabio Resinaro, in their feature film directorial debuts.
It stars Armie Hammer as a United States Marine who is walking on an unmapped minefield during a botched mission when one
fateful step makes his heart sink as he hears a click underfoot and tries to remain still until help arrives.
The film was released in the United States on April 7, 2017.
The film explores themes of waitress, babysitter,
revenge, police officer, left for dead.
The tone is emotional and intense.